(chuckles):
Get a load of this guy.
(Howard:)Can you imagine if we
make money with this?
(Leonard:)If we do,
I am splurging
(Leonard:)on the best sinus irrigator
money can buy.
(Howard:)That old sad story...
(Howard:)guy gets a little money,
goes straight up his nose.
(Attorney:)Just need you to review
and sign this document
(Attorney:)acknowledging that you
understand the university
(Attorney:)will own 75% of the patent.
75%?
(Sheldon:)That's outrageous.
(Sheldon:)This is our idea
based on our research.
(Sheldon:)How can you possibly justify
owning a majority share?
(Attorney:)It's university policy.
(Sheldon:)I know when I'm beat.
(Leonard:)Hold on, hold on.
So the three of us
(Leonard:)do all the work
and only end up with 25%?
(Attorney:)Dr. Hofstadter, this university
(Attorney:)has been paying your salaries
for over ten years.
(Attorney:)Did you think we do that out
of the goodness of our hearts?
(Leonard:)Well, until you just said
that mean thing, kinda.
(Attorney:)And as far as
Mr. Wolowitz is concerned,
(Attorney:)I'm afraid as a federal employee
on loan from NASA,
(Attorney:)your name can be
on the patent,
(Attorney:)but you're not entitled
to an ownership share.
(Howard:)Wait, so this can turn out to be
(Howard:)a financial success,
and I get nothing?
(Attorney:)Well, sometimes
they give you a plaque.
(Sheldon:)Well, that's not fair.
(Sheldon:)We should all get plaques.
(Leonard:)Sorry, but we
can't sign this.
(Howard:)Come on, let's go.
(Leonard:)Thank you for your time.
(Sheldon:)Couple of questions
about the plaque...
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪